Honore Niyitegeka

Full Stack Developer

■ nythonore@gmail.com 🤳 +250780455791 👂 Kigali Rwanda Kigali



Profile

Well-qualified full stack developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of frontend and backend development requirements. Handles any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering more than 3 years of related experience.

Experience

Senior Frontend Engineer

Feb 2022 - Present

Solution Social Network, Remote, United States

- Liaise with back-end developers, front-end developers, quality assurance testers, and CTO as needed.
- Develop web pages adhering to company standards, and assist the team to maintain strict standards.

Full Stack Developer

Aug 2021 - Present

Ishema Hub

- Collaborate with a team of 4 in-house web designers to create sleek and innovative UI design.
- Increase site traffic by 30% by developing user-oriented visuals and features using front-end languages, including HTML, CSS, and Typescript.
- Own more than 10 projects per year from initial research and conceptual design through testing and implementation phases.
- Author code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches.

Full Stack Developer

Dec 2020 - Aug 2021

Africa XYZ

- Improved website navigation boosting web traffic by 20%.
- Designed and executed security measures such as firewalls and encryption.,
- Developed landing pages, dashboards, and online applications using HMTL, CSS, and jQuery.
- Pulled from PHP, SQL, Javascript, and other back-end library knowledge to bolster programming resources.

Full Stack Developer

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

Upwork, Remote, United States

- Troubleshoot and debugged 10+ application codes for smooth execution and improved stability.
- Managed front-end development of client sites. Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to develop UI that raised dwell time by 35%.
- Worked with a variety of different languages, frameworks, and content management systems such as HTML, JavaScript, Django, WordPress, etc...

Personal details

Website nythonore.me

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/nythonore

Github github.com/nythonore

Skills

HTML, CSS / SASS, Javascript (ES6+), Typescript, TailwindCSS, React Admin

React, React Native, Next JS, Redux, Graphql, Node JS, Python, Django

Postgres, MongoDB, Redis

Docker, Kubernetes, CircleCI, AWS, GIT, NPM

Teamwork, Communication, Critical Thinking, Scrum / Agile

Education

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering

Adventist University of Central Africa, Kigali, Rwanda Mar 2020 - May 2022